and positive LegVio outcome trials next year,
will you have to use either a new sales force
or will you use an existing sales force,
that would be the one on LegVio,
some color also on the budget going forward?
Will you have to invest massively in marketing
to promote the new exacting clinical results?
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks, Laurent.
I think at the moment we would expect that for Pelacarsen
that we would be able to leverage the existing global LegVio field force
that we have.
Of course, usual adjustments that we might need
to make.
And I think the overall,
any investments that would be required for the Pelacarsen launch,
particularly around disease awareness to get additional patients tested
for LP little a levels,
we would be able to,
as all factored into the guidance that we've given on margin progression.
I think as we've noted in the past,
it will take time to drive up these biomarker testing rates,
but we're hopeful that we'll be able to do that.
We're hopeful that we'll be able to do that.
We're hopeful that we'll be able to do that with a drug that has a attractive efficacy
that will motivate physicians to test and ultimately patients to get on therapy.
I think for elsewhere in the cardiovascular portfolio,
obviously with avalacimab,
as well as the phase three program we'll be running with our NTIL-6
recently acquired medicine as well.
Those might require additional field force investments
and we'll, of course,
you know,
provide any guidance,
guidance on that once we get those phase three results and have a better read on those.
Those obviously go to different physician segments,
both for anticoagulation and in the case of the anti-IL-6,
patebecatug would be for physicians who are treating in the more acute coronary setting.
Good.
Thank you very much,
Raph.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of Colin White from UBS.
Please go ahead.
Hi, Colin White from UBS.
Thanks for taking my question.
Just on the stocking in the quarter,
we understand the 1% of sales beat was from stocking.
Cassanti explained some of this but not all of it.
So are you able to provide any color on what other drugs may have experienced stocking?
We'll go.
Yeah.